Guide to the Barry Mills Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Barry Mills Papers,
1933-1946
Mills, Andrew, 1875-1962.
10 v. (4 boxes)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
4079108
Biographical Note
Third president of the Dry Dock Savings Bank.
Scope and Content
Diaries of Andrew Mills, Jr., containing notations, drafts of speeches and essays, newspaper clippings, printed ephemera, and letters, all of which document and reflect the problems and changes in banking during the depression and war periods.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 3 series:
Sereis I: Cataloged Correspondence
Series II: Diaries
Series III: Scrapbook
Subjects
Dry Dock Savings Bank (New York, N.Y.); United States--Economic conditions.; Banks and banking--United States.; World War, 1939-1945.; Depressions--1929--United States.; Finance--United States.; Diaries.; Bankers.
Access Restrictions
The following boxes are located off-site: 2-4. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
This collection has no restrictions.
Access Restrictions
3 boxes of arranged material are shelved off-site and require advance notice of intent to use.
Acquisition
M-69 Alexander, Brooke Gift
- Sereis I: Cataloged Correspondence
  - Lehman, Herbert H. To Andrew Mills, Jr., Albany, 16 Aug 1938, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 1)
  - Lehman, Herbert H. To Andrew Mills, Jr., Albany, 19 Aug 1938, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 1)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr. To Andrew Mills, Jr., Washington, DC, 9 Oct 1941, (2 pages t.l.s.) (Box 1)
- Series II: Diaries
  - Diary,1933, 1936-1938 (Box 1)
  - Diary,1939-1940 (Box 2)
  - Diary,1941-1942 (Box 3)
  - Diary,1944-1945 (Box 4)
- Series III: Scrapbook
  - Scrapbook (Box 4)